John M. Webster fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Tynehead Zoological Society of BC, 1983 - 1986; F-222-5; 7 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to Webster's involvement on the Board of the Tynehead Zoological Society. Records include minutes, correspondence, meeting notes, and a manual.
  - Tynehead Zoological Society Board of Governors, 1985 - 1986; F-222-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 222-19)
  - Tynehead Zoological Society Board of Governors, 1983 - 1985; F-222-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 222-19)
  - Tynehead Zoological Society Manual, vol. 1, 1983 - 1984; F-222-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 222-19)
  - Tynehead Zoological Society Manual, vol. 2, 1983 - 1984; F-222-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 222-20)
- Reprints of Research articles, 1973 - 1993; F-222-7; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consist of copies of reprints of research articles authored or co-authored by Webster.
  - Reprints of research, vol. 1, [ca 1973] - [ca 1993]; F-222-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 222-25)
  - Reprints of research, vol. 2, [ca 1973] - [ca 1993]; F-222-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 222-25)
  - Reprints of research, vol. 3, [ca 1973] - [ca 1993]; F-222-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 222-25)
- Correspondence regarding Economic Nematology, 1969 - 1973; F-222-8; 31 cm of textual records 47 photographs.
  Series consists of records relating to editing Economic Nematology. Series is arranged in alphabetical order by name of contributor and includes correspondence, some drafts, and photographs.
  Graphic materials; Textual records
  - Blake, CD, 1971 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 222-25)
  - Cohn, F., 1971 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 222-25)
  - Eriksson, KB, 1971 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 222-25)
  - Hague, NGM, 1969 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Ichinohe, M., 1962 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Jensen, JH, 1969 - 1973; F-222-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Khan, MH, 1969 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Kort, J, 1969 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Lordello, LGE, 1970 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - McElroy, F, 1969 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Oostenbrink, M, 1969 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Prasad, SK, 1969 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Seshadri, AR, 1969 - 1971; F-222-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Webster, JM, 1970 - 1971; F-222-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Weischer, B, 1970 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - Winslow, RD, 1969 - 1972; F-222-8-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 222-26)
  - General items, 1969 - 1984; F-222-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 222-27)
  - Promotion, 1972; F-222-8-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 222-27)
  - Complimentary copies, 1972 - 1973; F-222-8-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 222-27)
  - Editing, 1969 - 1971; F-222-8-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 222-27)
  - Correspondence, 1969 - 1989; F-222-8-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 222-27)
  - Fenwick, D.W., 1969 - 1970; F-222-8-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 222-28)
  - Correspondence with publisher, 1972 - 1975; F-222-8-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 222-28)